and I, for example, am against the Unified State Examination, well,
а я например против ЕГЭ вот ну экзамены
we have exams like ZNO, and of course those
типа как ЗНО у нас да те экзамены
school exams. That is, I understand that
школьные конечно те То есть я понял то
you are in this party for the truth.
есть ты вы в партию вот эту за правду
Let’s go because you are against these school
Пошли потому что вы против этих школьных
exams.
экзаменов
Well, since our Communist
Да ну раз раз у нас Коммунистическая
Party has collapsed  Yes,
партия развалилась Да
but it’s close to me, that’s why you’re against eg
но близко мне вот а почему вы против эг
what again Why are you against
что ещё раз Почему вы против
eg eg what is it Well, you said
эгэ эг это что Ну вот вы же сказали
against you against what you
против вы против чего
said
сказали
Hello Hello, I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsk Where are
Хмельницке Вы
you from? I’m from the Moscow region, the city of
откуда Я из Подмосковья город
Elektrostal I understood this where it was that
Электросталь понял это там где было что
in short  two types for a boy scalp yes
короче два типа пацану скальп да
no in another city it was Well yes I saw
нет в другом городе была Ну да я видел
this
вот это
not in Elektrostal Well now I’m in or
вот не в Электростали Ну сечас я по или
from
из
Elektrostal not in Paskoye village in my opinion
Электростали нет в паском поса по-моему
or somewhere nearby Yes I
илито где-то рядом было Да
saw it
видел
under the lights
под подсв э
but this is just recently  in some other
а вот это недавно ещ в каком-то другом
city it was yes, but I remember that
городе было да А вот я помню что
Elektrostal was the first time I heard about such a
Электростали впервые услышал про такой
city, it’s like, in
город вот это что типу
short, it’s tough there.
короче там жёстко у
Yes, I don’t know,
вас Да не знаю
it’s
это
some kind of thing. What kind of flag is hanging there?
какие-то А у вас что там за флаг висит у
You have an interesting one, I see its edge
вас интересный я его край вижу
only for the truth and this is
только за правду а вот это
for the truth and what kind of party is
за правду а что это за партия
this Zakhar Prilep
какая-то Захар прилеп
Len Cool And you are Prilepine and you are
Лен Прикольно А вы прилепине а вы
Prilepine Well, yes, I’m a member of the party Ponia
прилепине Ну да я состою в партии Поня
Maybe you Well, I understand that Dasha
Может вам Ну я так понимаю что Даша
Dugina also meant something to you
Дугина тоже для вас что-то значила
Yes  I don’t know this one personally, I never knew one,
Да не знаю такую лично не знал никогда
but yes, well, there are a lot of people. What is
но да Ну там много кто В чём иде В чём
your idea? What is your
иде ваше
idea? What is the idea of ​​your
па В чём идея вашей
party? No, I like the fact that the
партии Не ну мне нравится то что в
creative people in it are close to me, like
ней творческие люди мне близкие как бы
super super, and the ideas of the party are. Well, these are
супер супер а идеи партии Какие Ну вот
good people.  it’s interesting to get drunk with them
хорошие люди побухать с ними интересно В
What are the ideas of the party? Yes Why
чём идеи партии Да Почем здесь побухать
not get drunk here? For example, I’m against the EG,
не побухать Вот я например против ЕГ вот
well, we have exams like the External Test, and those
ну экзамены типа как ЗНО у нас да те
school exams, of course. That is, I
экзамены школьные конечно То есть я
understand that you are joining this party for the
понял то есть ты вы в партию вот эту за
truth. Let’s go because you  against these
правду Пошли потому что вы против этих
school exams,
школьных экзаменов
yes, since our Communist Party
да раз раз у нас Коммунистическая партия
has collapsed
развалилась Да
Yes, but it’s close to me, that’s why you’re against
но близко мне вот а почему вы против
eg what again Why are you against eg
эгэ что ещё раз Почему вы против эг
what? Well, you said against what you said
это что Ну вот вы же сказали против вы
against what you said
против чего
not against what I didn’t say
сказали не против чего я не говорил
probably for that  what about the Unified State Exam Unified State Exam Yes, well,
наверное за то что а ЕГЭ ЕГЭ Да ну
because he makes some kind of robots out of children
потому что из детей Лепит Ну каких-то
Well, why robots Well, look The
роботов Ну а почему роботов Ну смотри
fact is that this exam allows the
Дело в том что этот экзамен позволяет
children to study in different schools And
дети учились в разных школах А оценивают
they are assessed according to one criterion and then it is clear who
их по одному критерию и тогда видно кто
can enter the University Yes, nothing  it’s
может поступить в Универси Да ничего там
not visible there it’s not visible that’s the point it’s not
не видно не видно вот в том-то и дело не
visible it’s we developed you know
видно это мы развивались понимаешь
what year of
какого года
birth seventy-nine seventy I’m
рождения семьдесят девятый семьдесят я
eighty-first Cool yes you
восемьдесят первый Прикольно да ите то
have that and And then you
есть и А вы потом по образованию кем
were
были
developed by education Well,
развитый Ну
if you omit all these, as it were, regalia
если вот эти все как бы регалия опустить
let there be a signalman signalman signalman
пусть будет связист связист связист
cool connection if you don’t lower the regalia
прикольно связ если с регалия не
Well, it took me a
Ну это очень
long time to understand it’s
долго понял
interesting Let’s Well, I
интересно Давайте Ну я
graduated from the
закончил
University of Communications and Informatics,
университет связи информатики
and well, that’s how this cell developed, it
и ну там вот этот сот так развивался это
started in 2000 20 years ago, everything took a long
начала 2000 20 лет назад очень всё долго
time, it seemed like it was going on for a long time.
долго как бы шло Вот и
Well, while we were developing and
Ну пока мы развивались и
learning by leaps and bounds, all communications and the
учились семимильными шагами вся связь и
Internet have gone far and
интернет ушли далеко и
for a long time. I believe that we have been studying
надолго Я считаю что мы изучаем
blockers for fifty-four years, well,
пятьдесят четвёртый год блокираторы ну
some uh-huh, somehow I understood it’s interesting,
какие-то угу както так понял интересно
yes Yes, it seems to me that it’s not at all interesting
да Да мне кажется совсем неинтересно что
what the square root of minus units is.
такое корень квадрат из минус единиц А
then we didn’t
что-то мы вообще не
meet at all Andronik me
познакомились Андроник меня
Andronik I’m just a Greek Greek name
Андроник Я просто грек греческое имя
Greek Yes, a Greek by nationality is generally a Greek
грек Да грек по национальности обще грек
against the
на
background of a citizen of Ukraine a citizen of Ukraine
фоне гражданин Украины гражданин Украины
And that is, I need to hang a Polish Jewish flag in the back, I
А то есть мне взади надо а польский
know Polish I don’t know where
повесить польский знаю Я не знаю откуда
you are from Look at the question, I understand that  you
вы Смотри вопрос я так понимаю что вы вы
know, I said that I’m from Russia, I
знаете я же сказал что я с России я
understand, I’m interested, look, that is,
понял я эг мне интересно смотри То есть
now children are dumbed down by these exams But
сейчас детей отупляет этими экзаменами А
we had a good
вот у нас было хорошее
education, well, it was free, yes And
образование ну оно было свободное да А
now I understand the word and now it’s points points
сейчас слово понял а сейчас это баллы
points points points points And
баллы баллы балы балы А
before  Well, before, a person could
раньше ну а раньше человек может мог
enter any university on his own; before, he could do the same himself,
поступить сам в любой университет раньше
and now he can
сам мог поступить так и сейчас может
pass on the basis of points, you know,
сдал за счётом баллов понимаешь
but I scored, my eldest daughter is
да вот набрал вот у меня старшая дочка
already 19 years old. It’s good that she
19 лет она уже Это хорошо что она
entered Saratov University
поступила в Саратовский университет
for free, well, the youngest is 10.  as if
бесплатный вот ну младшие 10 вот как бы
everything is still ahead I hope that this
ещё всё впереди Я надеюсь что вот это
Yaga will be removed But the question I don’t quite
Яга уберут А вот вопрос я не совсем
remember is these formulas:
помню вот эти формулы если у квадрата
if a square has a side of 3 cm, what is its area? Are you a mathematician? Well, I forgot this formula, if a square has a side of 3 cm, what is its
если у квадрата сторона 3 см какая его
area? Well  For example, you
пло забыл Ну я например
can just say I’m interested in
можете сказать просто мне интересно
what the area of ​​a square will be if it has a
какая будет площадь квадрата если у неё
side, it’s not interesting at all, well, it’s
сторона это вообще неинтересно ну с
just interesting for me, well, for me it’s
просто интересно для меня ну для меня
not interesting at all, just in case,
вообще не интересно на всякий случай
a humanities student, how much area will be higher than a
гуманитарий сколько будет площ выше
signalman,
связист связи
if a square has a side of 3 cm
если квадрат у которого сторона 3 см
What is the area of ​​this
Какая площадь этого
square Great, well, well, well, well, what is
квадрата Здорово ну ну ну и ну Какая
the area? I’m asking you, so I understand
площадь Я вас спрашиваю вот я понимаю
that ege now Yes, they ask me Well,
что эгэ сечас Да меня спрашивают Ну ну
that’s ege This is bad, yes Because children
вот это эгэ Это плохо да Потому что дети
take exams and then go to university based on these
сдают экзамены и потом поступают по этим
scores, but you and I were
баллам в университет а вот мы же с вами
still studying  in the Soviet Union, but you are in the
учились ещё в Советском Союзе но вы
seventy-ninth year, I am the eighty-
семьдесят девятого года я восемьдесят
first I studied a little poorly at school
первого Я немножко плохо в школе учился
and I don’t remember this formula How to find
и не помню вот эту формулу Как найти
the area of ​​a square with a side of
площадь квадрата со стороной
3 so I say once again
3 так я ещё раз говорю
a humanities person so how to find Well, I don’t know
гуманитарий так как найти Ну я не знаю
how to stab the ax but  ok, well, how does
как-то заху колить надо а хорошо а как
pi multiply by pi How to find the area
ну там пи на пи множится Как найти площ
Well, pi by pi you need to multiply and it will be pi by
Ну пи на пи надо умножить и будет пи на
pi Yes, I understand, yes yes yes, then I understand
пи Да понял да да да то я так понимаю
that if you remove it, then it will be
что если убрать эг то вообще будет
true like yours,
правда как у вас
but how to find the area of ​​a square, they removed it
а как найти площадь квадрата так убрали
Xyu Tell me how to find the area of ​​a square with a
сю Скажите как найти площадь квадрата со
side of 3
стороной 3
if we
сли у нас
have ZNO
з ЗНО
externally independent
внешне независимое
assessment with the
оценивание с
loa of a square with RONO 3
лоа квадрата со РОНО 3
cm write to mi Telegram directly immediately axis
см пись на мий Telegram прямо зараз ось
VN
ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube Zaga
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube Зага
us through the skarg ORV in your ban and even more
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
richly  I don’t show the video to people at all times, I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about the streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we can write an operational link
того щоб мы оперативный звязок пишиться
right away and Popik there in Telegra okrim
прямо зараз а Попик там в телегра окрим
video also tezh Tsikava and Korisna information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we are sorry for you trimati postiyny
и ми повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational link in the same time,
оперативный звязок незалежно в того чи
show you the process YouTube  Glory to Ukraine
покаже вам проце YouTube Слава украини
letter
пись а